这没什么好说的
There's nothing to tell!
他不过是我的同事
He's just some guy I work with!
少来了  你们都在约会了
C'mon, you're going out with the guy!
这个男人一定有什么问题
There's gotta be something wrong with him!
他是驼背吗  戴着假发的驼背
So does he have a hump? A hump and a hairpiece?
等等  他吃粉笔吗
Wait, does he eat chalk?
我只是不想你
Just, 'cause, I don't want her to go through
重蹈我和卡尔的覆辙
what I went through with Carl
拜托各位  放松点  这甚至不算是约会
Okay, everybody relax. This is not even a date.
只不过是两个人出去吃个饭
It's just two people going out to dinner
而且不会上床
and not having sex.
听起来像是和我约会
Sounds like a date to me.
于是我回到了高中学校
Alright, so I'm back in high school,
我站在食堂中间
I'm standing in the middle of the cafeteria
然后发现自己全身赤裸
and I realize I am totally naked.
噢  做过那种梦
Oh, yeah. Had that dream.
然后我低下头  看见那里有一部
Then I look down, and I realize there's a phone
大哥大
there.
-那话儿变成了  -没错
- Instead of...?  - That's right.
-这种梦倒从未做过  -没有
- Never had that dream. - No.
突然  那电话响起来了
All of a sudden, the phone starts to ring.
结果是我妈打来的
And it turns out it's my mother,
这非常非常奇怪
which is very-very weird because-
因为她从来不打电话给我
she never calls me!
嗨
Hi.
这家伙一张嘴打招呼  我就想自杀
This guy says hello, I wanna kill myself.
你还好吧  亲爱的
Are you okay, sweetie?
我感觉有人把手伸入我的喉咙
I just feel like someone reached down my throat
抓住我的小肠
grabbed my small intestine,
从我嘴里扯出来
pulled it out of my mouth
然后缠在我脖子上
and tied it around my neck...
饼干
Cookie?
卡罗尔今天把她的东西搬走了
Carol moved her stuff out today
-我帮你泡杯咖啡  -谢了
- Let me get you some coffee.  - Thanks.
不  不要  别再净化我的灵气了
No, no don't! Stop cleansing my aura!
求你了  别碰我的灵气  好吗
No, just leave my aura alone, okay?
我会没事的  好吧
I'll be fine, alright?
真的  各位  我希望她能幸福
Really, everyone. I hope  she'll be very happy.
-不  你不会  -没错  我不会的
- No you don't. - No I don't,
去她的  她甩掉了我
to hell with her, she left me!
你又不知道她是女同性恋
And you never knew she was a lesbian...
不知道  行了吧
No!! Okay?!
为何大家都绕着这个话题打转
Why does everyone keep fixating on that?
她都不知道  我怎么会知道
She didn't know, how should I know?
有时我希望自己也是个女同性恋
Sometimes I wish I was a lesbian...
我大声说出来了么
Did I say that out loud?
好了罗斯  瞧
Alright Ross, look.
你现在很痛苦
You're feeling a lot of pain right now.
你很生气  很伤心
You're angry. You're hurting.
要不要我给你支一招
Can I tell you what the answer is?
脱衣舞俱乐部
Strip joint!
别这样  作为光棍儿  爷们起来
C'mon, you're single! Have some hormones!
我不想单身的  好吗
I don't want to be single, okay?
我只想  再次结婚
I just...I just wanna be married again!
而我只想要一百万美金
And I just want a million dollars!
瑞秋
Rachel?!
噢  天啊  莫妮卡  嗨  谢天谢地
Oh,God, Monica, hi! Thank God!
我刚去了你家  可你不在
I just went to your building and you weren't there
有个拿大锤子的家伙说你可能会在这儿
and then this guy with a big hammer said you might be here
结果你真的在这儿 你真的在这儿
and you are, you are!
-要来杯咖啡吗  -无咖啡因的
- Can I get you some coffee?  - De-Caff
好了  各位  这是瑞秋
Okay, everybody, this is Rachel,
另一位林肯高中的幸存者
another Lincoln High survivor.
这就是各位啦  这是钱德勒
This is everybody, this is Chandler,
菲比  还有乔伊
and Phoebe, and Joey,
还记得我哥哥罗斯吗
and you remember my brother Ross?
-当然  嗨  -嗨
- Hi, sure! - Hi.
你是想现在跟我们说说
So you wanna tell us now
还是我们再等四位湿漉漉的伴娘过来
or are we waiting for four wet bridesmaids?
噢  上帝  好吧
Oh, God...well,
大概在婚礼前半个小时
it started about a half hour before the wedding.
我当时在存放礼品的房间里
I was in the room where we were keeping all the presents,
看着调味汁瓶
and I was looking at this gravy boat.
那是一件极其美丽的里摩日细瓷调味汁瓶
This really gorgeous Limoges gravy boat.
然后  突然间
When all of a sudden
有糖吗
Sweet 'n' Lo?
我发现我对这个调味汁瓶
I realized that I was more turned on
比巴瑞更能引发我的兴奋感
by this gravy boat than by Barry!
然后我真的吓坏了
And then I got really freaked out,
突然想到
and that's when it hit me:
巴瑞真的超像薯头先生
how much Barry looks like Mr. Potato Head.
我是说  我总是觉得他眼熟
Y'know, I mean, I always knew looked familiar,
但是
but...
不管怎么说  我必须离开那里
Anyway, I just had to get out of there,
我开始想
and I started wondering
"我干吗这么做  我这么做是为了谁"
"Why am I doing this, and who am I doing this for?"
不管怎么说  我不知该去哪里
So anyway I just didn't know where to go,
而且我知道我们有点疏远了
and I know that you and I have kinda drifted apart,
但是  你是我在这个城市
but you're the only person I knew
唯一认识的人
who lived here in the city.
还没有被邀请参加婚礼
Who wasn't invited to the wedding.
噢  我希望这不是个问题
Ooh, I was kinda hoping that wouldn't be an issue...
我猜他送她一台管风琴
Now I'm guessing that he bought her the big pipe organ,
而她很不喜欢
and she's really not happy about it.
爸爸  我只是  不能嫁给他
Daddy, I just... I can't marry him!
对不起  我只是不爱他
I'm sorry. I just don't love him.
可是对我来说就有关系
Well, it matters to me!
噢  她真不应该穿那条裤子
Ooh, she should not be wearing those pants.
要我说  推她下楼
I say push her down the stairs.
推她下楼  把推她下楼  把推她下楼
Push her down the stairs! Push her down the stairs! Push her down the stairs!
爸  你听我说
C'mon Daddy, listen to me!
这就好像  在我一生中
It's like, it's like, all of my life,
所有人都一直告诉我"你是一只鞋子
everyone has always told me, 'You're a shoe!
你是鞋子  你是鞋子  你是鞋子
You're a shoe, you're a shoe, you're a shoe!'.
可今天我停下来说
And today I just stopped and I said,
"如果我不想成为一只鞋呢"
'What if I don't wanna be a shoe?
如果我想当一个包包  或是一顶帽子呢
What if I wanna be a- a purse, y'know? Or a- or a hat!
不  我不是要你给我买帽子
No, I'm not saying I want you to buy me a hat,
我说我是一顶帽子
I'm saying I am a ha-
这是比喻啦  爸爸
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
这就是他的问题所在了
You can see where he'd have trouble.
听着爸爸  这是我的人生
Look Daddy, it's my life.
也许我可以和莫妮卡住在一起
Well maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
我猜和莫妮卡一起住的人选已然敲定了
Well, I guess we've established who's staying here with Monica...
也许那是我的决定
Well, maybe that's my decision.
也许我不需要你的钱
Well, maybe I don't need your money.
等等我说也许
Wait!! Wait, I said maybe!!
深呼吸
Just breathe, breathe...that's it.
就这样试着想些美好平静的事物
Just try to think of nice calm things...
玫瑰上的雨滴  小兔子和小猫咪
Rain drops on roses and rabbits and kittens
还有风铃草  雪橇铃  和啥啥的手套
bluebells and sleighbells and something with mittens...
啦啦啦  啥啥和绳子串起的面条
La la la something and noodles with string.
还有一些
These are a few...
我现在好多了
I'm all better now.
我帮上忙啦
I helped!
瞧  或许这样反倒最好
Okay, look, this is probably for the best, y'know?
你独立了  可以主宰自己的人生
Independence. Taking control of your life.
如有任何需求  尽管来找乔伊
And hey, you need anything, you can always come to Joey.
我和钱德勒就住在对面
Me and Chandler live across the hall.
而且他经常不在家
And he's away a lot.
乔伊  别再勾引她了
Joey, stop hitting on her!
今天是她结婚的日子
It's her wedding day!
怎么啦  难道还有什么明文规定不成
What, like there's a rule or something?
请不要在这么干了  这声音很烦人
Please don't do that again, it's a horrible sound.
我是保罗
It's, uh, it's Paul.
让他进来
Buzz him in.
-保罗是谁  -调酒的那个保罗吗
- Who's Paul? - Paul the Wine Guy, Paul?
也许吧
Maybe.
等等  你今晚的"非正式约会"对象
Wait. Your 'not a real date' tonight
是调酒师保罗
is with Paul the Wine Guy?
-他终于开口约你了吗  -是的
- He finally asked you out?  - Yes!
噢  这真是值得永久铭记的时刻
Ooh, this is a Dear Diary moment.
瑞秋  我可以取消
Rach, wait, I can cancel...
不  你去吧我没事
Please, no, go, that'd be fine!
罗斯  你没事吧你要我留下来吗
Are, are you okay? I mean, do you want me to stay?
那样最好
That'd be good...
-真的吗  -才怪 去吧
- Really? - No, go on!
那可是调酒师保罗
It's Paul the Wine Guy!
嗨  请进  保罗  这是
Hi, come in! Paul, this is...
大家  各位  这是保罗
...everybody, everybody, this is Paul.
-嘿  保罗  -你好
- Hey! Paul! - Hello!
嗨  调酒师
Hi! The Wine Guy!
抱歉  没听清你的名字  保罗  是吗
I'm sorry, I didn't catch your name. Paul, was it?
好了  坐会  马上就好
Okay, sit down. Two seconds.
噢  我刚拔掉四根睫毛  不是好兆头
Ooh, I just pulled out four eyelashes. That can't be good.
瑞秋  你  你今晚打算怎么过
So Rachel, what're you, uh... what're you up to tonight?
这个嘛  本来我应该
Well, I was kinda supposed to be
在阿鲁巴岛度蜜月  所以  没事做
headed for Aruba on my honeymoon, so nothing!
对哦  你都不能去度蜜月  上帝
Right, you're not even getting your honeymoon, God..
不过在阿鲁巴岛的这个时候  说到你的
No, no, although, Aruba, this time of year... talk about your
大蜥蜴
big lizards...
不管怎样如果你今晚不想独处的话
Anyway, if you don't feel like being alone tonight,
乔伊和钱德勒要到我那儿
Joey and Chandler are coming over to help me
帮我组合新家具
put together my new furniture.
是呀  我们特别期待特别兴奋
Yes, and we're very excited about it.
真的很感谢
Well actually thanks,
不过我今晚想待在这儿
but I think I'm just gonna hang out here tonight.
-今天真的很漫长  -好吧  当然了
- It's been kinda a long day. - Okay, sure.
菲比你想来帮忙吗
Hey, Pheebs, you wanna help?
我倒希望能去帮忙  但我不想去
Oh, I wish I could, but I don't want to.
我应该用一套这样的小蜗杆
I'm supposed to attach a brackety thing to the side things,
将托架装在侧面
using a bunch of these little worm guys.
但我没看见托架  也没有看见什么蜗杆
I have no brackety thing, I see no whim guys whatsoever
而且我的腿麻了
and I cannot feel my legs.
这是什么
What's this?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
-书架做好了  -全部完工
- Done with the bookcase!  - All finished!
这是卡罗尔最爱喝的啤酒
This was Carol's favorite beer.
她总是不用易拉罐喝  我该知道
She always drank it out of the can, I should have known.
罗斯  我问你一个问题
Ross, let me ask you a question.
她得到了家具  音响和很棒的电视机
She got the furniture, the stereo, the good TV-
你得到什么
what did you get?
你们
You guys.
-天啊  -你被坑了
- Oh, my God. - You got screwed.
天哪
Oh my God!
-天哪  -我知道  我是个大白痴
- Oh my God! - I know, I know, I'm such an idiot.
她每周看四五次牙医时
I guess I should have caught on when
我心里就该有数了
she started going to the dentist four and five times a week.
我是说  牙齿能需要多干净呢
I mean, how clean can teeth get?
我哥也碰到这种事了  他也很纠结
My brother's going through that right now, he's such a mess.
你是怎么熬过来的
How did you get through it?
你可以尝试  不小心砸烂她贵重的东西
Well, you might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers,
-比如她的  -腿
- say her... - ...leg?
那也是种选择  至于我嘛
That's one way! Me, I-
我砸烂了她的表
I went for the watch.
你真的把她的表弄坏了
You actually broke her watch?
巴瑞  对不起  真是对不起
Barry, I'm sorry... I am so sorry...
你一定认为这件事跟
I know you probably think that this is all about
我那天说你穿着袜子做爱有关
what I said the other day about you making love with your socks on,
其实不是  是我的原因  我只是
but it isn't... it isn't, it's about me, and I just...
喂  电话又断了
Hi, machine cut me off again...
不管怎样  听着
anyway...look, look,
你知道最可怕的是什么
You know what the scariest part is?
万一人这一辈子只有一个女人怎么办
What if there's only one woman for everybody, y'know?
我是说如果你找了个女人
I mean what if you get one woman-
然后就此过一生
and that's it?
不幸的是  我唯一的女人爱的是  女人
Unfortunately in my case, there was only one woman- for her...
你说什么呢  "一个女人"
What are you talking about? 'One woman'?
这就像是在说  你只能吃一种冰淇淋口味
That's like saying there's only one flavor of ice cream for you.
让我告诉你  罗斯  还有很多种口味
Lemme tell you something, Ross. There's lots of flavors out there.
有巧克力坚果味  曲奇味还有香草味
There's Rocky Road, and Cookie Dough, and Bing! Cherry Vanilla.
还可以和糖条  果仁  或者奶油一起吃
You could get 'em with Jimmies, or nuts, or whipped cream!
这简直是你一生中最大的喜事
This is the best thing that ever happened to you!
你难道是八岁结的婚吗
You got married, you were, like, what, eight?
欢迎回到现实世界  拿起勺子开挖吧
Welcome back to the world! Grab a spoon!
我真不晓得现在自己是真饿了还是欲火难耐
I honestly don't know if I'm hungry or horny.
离我的冰箱远点
Stay out of my freezer!
自从她甩掉我之后  我就
Ever since she walked out on me, I, uh...
怎么了  你打算边搅面条边讲吗
What?... What, you wanna spell it out with noodles?
不  这该是第五次约会时候才说的事儿
No, it's, it's more of a fifth date kinda revelation.
噢  这么说会有第五次约会了
Oh, so there is gonna be a fifth date?
你不想吗
Isn't there?
想  我想的
Yeah... yeah, I think there is.
你刚才想说什么
What were you gonna say?
好吧  自从她离开后
Well, ever-ev-... ever since she left me,
我就一直无法过
um, I haven't been able to, uh, perform.
性生活
...Sexually.
天啊  天啊  对不起
Oh, God, Oh, God, I am sorry...
-真不好意思  -没事  没事
- I am so sorry... - It's okay...
我知道你现在需要的必然不是被人喷一身水
I know being spit on is probably not what you need right now.
-多久了  -两年了
- Um... how long? - Two years.
我真高兴你砸烂了她的表
Wow! I'm-I'm-I'm glad you smashed her watch!
那你还想要第五次约会吗
So you still think you, um... might want that fifth date?
是的  我希望有
...Yeah. Yeah, I do.
看  乔安妮是爱卡奇的
Oh...see... but Joanne loved Chachi!
这就是不同
That's the difference!
"拿起勺子"
Grab a spoon.
你知道我拿起勺子多久了吗
Do you know how long it's been since I've grabbed a spoon?
难道"比利  别逞英雄"这句话对你没意义
Do the words 'Billy, don't be a hero' mean anything to you?
还有个问题
Y'know, here's the thing.
就算我鼓足了勇气  想约个女人出来
Even if I could get it together enough to- to ask a woman out,...
我又能约谁呢
who am I gonna ask?
不可思议吧
Isn't this amazing?
我这辈子从没泡过咖啡
I mean, I have never made coffee before in my entire life.
-真不可思议  -恭喜你了
- That is amazing. - Congratulations.
既然你现在正进入角色
While you're on a roll
有没有想做个煎蛋卷之类的东西
If you feel like you have to make a Western omelet or something..
不过事实上我还不太饿
Although actually I'm really not that hungry...
-早安  -早安
- Morning. - Good morning.
-早安  -早安  保罗
- Morning. - Morning, Paul.
-你好保罗  -嗨  保罗是吧
- Hello, Paul. - Hi, Paul, is it?
-谢谢  太感谢你了  -不要这样
- Thank you. Thank you so much. - Stop.
晚点联系
We'll talk later.
谢谢你
Yeah. Thank you.
那还不叫真正的约会
That wasn't a real date?!
那你真正的约会到底要干些什么
What the hell do you do on a real date?
-闭嘴  把桌子抬回去  -好啦
- Shut up, and put my table back. - Okayyy!
好了孩子们  我必须上班去了
All right, kids, I gotta get to work.
但如果我不输入那些数字
If I don't input those numbers...
也没什么关系
it doesn't make much of a difference...
你们大伙儿都有工作
So, like, you guys all have jobs?
对  我们都有工作
Yeah, we all have jobs.
这样才有钱买东西
See, that's how we buy stuff.
对  我是个演员
Yeah, I'm an actor.
你演过什么  我看过吗
Wow! Would I have seen you in anything?
难说  大部分范围都挺小的
I doubt it. Mostly regional work.
等下  除非你碰巧看过
Oh wait, wait, unless you happened to catch the
《匹诺曹》的重播
Reruns' production of Pinocchio.
"瞧  盖佩多  我是真正的小男孩了"
'Look, Gippetto, I'm a real live boy.'
-别这么侮辱人  -你说得对  对不起
-  I will not take this abuse.  - You're right, I'm sorry.
"我曾是个小木偶  小木偶"
"Once I was a wooden boy, a little wooden boy..."
今天感觉如何
So how you doing today?
睡得还好吧  跟巴瑞谈过了吗
Did you sleep okay? Talk to Barry?
我无法停止笑
I can't stop smiling.
看得出来
I can see that.
你活像昨晚睡觉时嘴里放了个撑衣架
You look like you slept with a hanger in your mouth.
我知道  他是那么
I know, he's just so, so...
还记得你和托尼·德马科吗
Do you remember you and Tony DeMarco?
记得啊
Oh, yeah.
就像那样  那种感觉
Well, it's like that. With feelings.
-哇  你真是有麻烦了
- Wow,are you in trouble!
好啦  好啦  我要站起来  去工作
Okay. Okay. I am just going to get up, go to work
而且一整天都不要想他
and not think about him all day.
或者只是站起来去工作
Or else I'm just gonna get up and go to work.
-祝我好运  -为什么
- Oh, look, wish me luck! - What for?
我要去找那个工作什么的东西
I'm gonna go get one of those job things.
嘿  莫妮卡
Hey, Monica!
嘿  弗兰妮  欢迎回来
Hey Frannie, welcome back!
在佛罗里达过得如何
How was Florida?
你做爱了  对不
You had sex, didn't you?
-你怎么知道的
- How do you do that?
那么  和谁
So? Who?
你认识保罗吧
You know Paul?
保罗  那个调酒的
Paul the Wine Guy?
对  我认识保罗
Oh yeah, I know Paul.
你是说你认识他就像我认识他一样
You mean you know Paul like I know Paul?
开玩笑吧  保罗还欠我一个人情呢
Are you kidding? I take credit for Paul.
遇到我之前他已有两年无法过性生活
Y'know before me, there was no snap in his turtle for two years.
显然他是骗你的
Of course it was a line!
为什么  为什么会有人那样做
Why?! Why? Why, why would anybody do something like that?
我想你是想让我们拿出一个
I assume we're looking for an answer more sophisticated
比"想和你上床"更为复杂的回答
than 'to get you into bed'.
问题出在我身上
Is it me?
难道我身上带着某种味儿
Is it like I have some sort of beacon
只有狗和有严重情感问题的男人才会发觉吗
that only dogs and men with severe emotional problems can hear?
好啦  过来  把你的脚给我
All right, c'mere, gimme your feet.
我只是以为他是个好男人
I just thought he was nice, y'know?
我真不相信  你不知道那是个谎言
I can't believe you didn't know it was a line!
-猜猜怎么了  -你找到工作了
- Guess what?  - You got a job?
开玩笑吗  我什么都不会
Are you kidding? I'm trained for nothing!
今天十二个面试  我都是被嘲笑轰出来的
I was laughed out of twelve interviews today.
不过你却异常兴奋
And yet you're surprisingly upbeat.
如果你遇见"约翰&大卫"的皮靴打五折
You would be too if you found John and David boots on sale,
也会跟我一样的
fifty percent off!
是呀  你多了解我啊
Oh, how well you know me...
这就是  我不需要工作
They're my new 'I don't need a job,
不需要父母  一双好皮靴足矣
I don't need my parents, I've got great boots' boots!
你怎么付的款
How'd you pay for them?
用信用卡
Uh, credit card.
那谁付账单
And who pays for that?
我爸啊
Um... my... father.
拜托  你不能靠你爸一辈子
C'mon, you can't live off your parents your whole life.
我知道  这就是为什么我要结婚
I know that. That's why I was getting married.
饶了她吧  第一次独立并不轻松
Give her a break, it's hard being on your own for the first time.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气  我记得我第一次来纽约时的情景
You're welcome. I remember when I first came to this city.
当时我十四岁
I was fourteen.
我妈刚自杀  我继父再度入狱
My mom had just killed herself and my step-dad was back in prison,
我来到这里  举目无亲
and I got here, and I didn't know anybody.
最后我和一个白化病患者住在一起
And I ended up living with this albino guy who was, like,
他给港务局的人清洗车窗玻璃
cleaning windshields outside port authority,
后来他也自杀了
and then he killed himself,
然后我成了按摩师
and then I found aromatherapy.
所以相信我  我完全了解你的感受
So believe me, I know exactly how you feel.
你想要说的话是
The word you're looking for is
"无论如何"
"Anyway"...
好了准备好了吗
All right, you ready?
-我不这么想
- I don't think so.
剪掉  剪掉  剪掉
C'mon, cut. Cut, cut, cut,...
欢迎来到现实世界
Welcome to the real world!
它糟透了  但你会喜欢的
It sucks. You're gonna love it!
好啦  你要睡在沙发上吗
Well, that's it. You gonna crash on the couch?
不  我要回家
No. No, I gotta go home sometime.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You be okay?  - Yeah.
莫妮卡  看我在地板上发现了什么
Hey Mon, look what I just found on the floor.
什么
What?
那是保罗的表
That's Paul's watch.
放回原地就好了
You just put it back where you found it. Oh boy
-好吧  晚安各位  -晚安
- Alright. Goodnight, everybody.  - Goodnight.
-对不起  -不不  你来
- Sorry-  - No no no, go-
不不  你吃吧  真的  我不想吃
No, you have it, really, I don't want it
-分着吃  -好吧
- Split it?  - Okay.
你大概不知道
You know you probably didn't know this,
我在高中时  曾经
but back in high school, I had a, um,
暗恋过你
major crush on you.
我知道
I knew.
你知道  哦
You did! Oh....
我还以为你一直认为
I always figured you just thought
我是莫妮卡的怪哥哥呢
I was Monica's geeky older brother.
的确如此
I did.
听着  你是不是认为
Oh. Listen, do you think
不要太在意我
and try not to let my intense vulnerability
脆弱的心灵
become any kind of a factor here
但是你觉得我能约你出去吗
but do you think it would be okay if I asked you out?
偶尔  有可能吗
Sometime? Maybe?
当然  或许
Yeah, maybe...
好  好  或许我会的
Okay... okay, maybe I will...
-晚安  -晚安
- Goodnight.  - Goodnight.
再见
See ya....
等等  你怎么了
Waitwait, what's the deal?
我刚刚拿起了勺子
I just grabbed a spoon.
我真不敢相信我的耳朵
I can't believe what I'm hearing here.
I can't believe what I'm hearing here...
怎么了  我说你有一个
What? I-I said you had a
我说你有一个
What I said you had...
你能不能不这么干
Would you stop?
-噢  我又来了  -是的
- Oh, was I doing it again?  - Yes!
有人要咖啡吗
Would anybody like more coffee?
是你冲的  还是你端来的
Did you make it, or are you just serving it?
-我端来的  -好吧  给我来杯咖啡
- I'm just serving it.  - Yeah. Yeah, I'll have a cup of coffee.
孩子们  我又做新梦了
Kids, new dream...
我在拉斯维加斯
I'm in Las Vegas.
我是丽莎·明妮莉
I'm Liza Minelli-